export const  data =[

{
    question:"What is the correct command to create a new React project?",
    option1:"npm create-react-app",
    option2:"npx create-react-app",
    option3:"npm create-react-app myReactApp",
    option4:"npx create-react-app myReactApp ",
    ans:4
},
{
    question:"npx create-react-app myReactApp",
    option1:"The directory to create the new app in",
    option2:"A reference to an existing app",
    option3:"The name you want to use for the new app",
    option4:"The type of App to create",
    ans:3
},
{
    question:"What command is used to start the React local development server?",
    option1:"npm build",
    option2:"npm start",
    option3:"npm serve",
    option4:"npm run dev",
    ans:2
},{
    question:"What is the default local host port that a React development server uses?",
    option1:"5173",
    option2:"8080",
    option3:"3000",
    option4:"3504",
    ans:3
},{
    question:"Which keyword creates a constant in JavaScript?",
    option1:"const",
    option2:"let",
    option3:"constant",
    option4:"var",
    ans:1
},{
    question:"A copy of the 'real' DOM that is kept in memory is called what?",
    option1:"DOM",
    option2:"React DOM",
    option3:"Virtual DOM ",
    option4:"Shadow DOM",
    ans:3
},{
    question:"Which operator can be used to conditionally render a React component?",
    option1:"?? ",
    option2:"||",
    option3:"::",
    option4:"&&",
    ans:4
},{
    question:"When rendering a list using the JavaScript map() method, what is required for each element rendered?",
    option1:"data",
    option2:"key",
    option3:"id",
    option4:"index",
    ans:2
},{
    question:"What tool does React use to compile JSX?",
    option1:"ReactDOM  ",
    option2:"JSX Compiler",
    option3:"Babel ",
    option4:"React Router",
    ans:3
},{
    question:"What props will be available to :<Car {...props} />?",
    option1:"children  ",
    option2:"all of them",
    option3:"only updated ones",
    option4:"only static ones",
    ans:2
},{
    question:"What is a common use case for ref?",
    option1:"To refer to another JavaScript file",
    option2:"To directly access a DOM node",
    option3:"To refer to a function",
    option4:"To bind the function",
    ans:2
},{
    question:"What is the correct syntax to import a Component from React?",
    option1:"import { Component } from 'react'",
    option2:"import [ Component ] from 'react'",
    option3:"import React.Component from 'react'",
    option4:"import Component from 'react'",
    ans:1
},{
    question:"React separates the user interface into components. How are components combinded to create a user interface?",
    option1:"By nesting components",
    option2:"With webpack",
    option3:"By putting them in a folder structure",
    option4:"With code splitting",
    ans:1
},

] 